Guide to the UE District 11 Records, 1940s-1990s UE.15.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE District 11 Records
1940s-1990s
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 11
UE.15.11
255 Linear Feet (204 boxes)
District 11 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) included locals in the Chicago and Milwaukee area. This subgroup contains correspondence, subject files, membership cards, and publications regarding District 11 locals, companies, and research.
Scope and Content Notes
This subgroup contains correspondence, subject files, membership cards, and publications regarding District 11 locals, companies, and research. Files include information on local contracts, organization efforts, and district council meetings. Membership cards and lists are also present, as well as copies of the Chicago UE News.
Arrangement
This subgroup has not yet been arranged, however approximately half of the collection has been inventoried at the box level and the collection is open for research. Please contact the Archives Service Center for more information.
Access Restrictions
Records of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) are closed for a period of twenty-five years after their creation.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America, District 11 in 1994, 1997, 2006.
Previous Citation
UE District 11 Records, 1940s-1990s, UE.15.11, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Related Material
UE National Office Records Relating to District 11 and District 11 Locals, 1936-1990s, UE.4.1.11, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- Middle West -- History; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- History; Membership cards; Publications; Correspondence; Labor; Chicago (Ill.); Labor unions -- Middle West -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; DeMaio, Ernest; Rosen, Frank; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 11; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
- Local Records, 1956-1961 (Box 1)
- Local Records, 1960-1961 (Box 2)
- Local Records, 1946-1962 (Box 3)
- Constitutions, 1944-1957 (Box 4, Folder 1-2)
- District Council Minutes, 1956-1959 (Box 4, Folder 3-9)
- Correspondence, Ernest DeMaio, 1943-1959 (Box 4, Folder 10-17)
- Correspondence, General, 1946-1959 (Box 4, Folder 18-19)
- Finances, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Organization: Victor Products, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Organization: United Specialties, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Organization: Teletype, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 23-25)
- Organization: Triplex, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Organization: Majestic Radio, 1941-1946 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Organization: Northwestern Electric, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Organization: Sheridan Electric, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Organization: Utah Speaker, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Organization: J.P. Seeburg, 1944-1945 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Organization: Moline Tod, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Organization: Triumph Mfg., 1942 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Organization: Hurley Washing Machine, 1942-1943 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Organization: Scott Radio, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 35-36)
- Organization: Sangamon Electric/Inter-union Rivalry, 1943-1949 (Box 4, Folder 37-44)
- Constitutions: Farm Equipment Workers, 1940-1949 (Box 4, Folder 45-52)
- Constitutions: International Longshoremen & Warehousemen, 1943-1947 (Box 4, Folder 53)
- Constitutions: Congress of Industrial Organizations, 1940-1952 (Box 4, Folder 54-62)
- Constitutions: National Maritime Union, 1943-1948 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Constitutions: United Office and Professional Workers, 1942-1948 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Constitutions: United Furniture Workers, 1939-1948 (Box 4, Folder 63-66)
- Constitutions: IUE, 1949-1959 (Box 4, Folder 67-69)
- Constitutions: Fur and Leather Workers, 1943-1948 (Box 4, Folder 70)
- Constitutions: Mine Mill & Smelter Workers, 1943-1948 (Box 4, Folder 71-75)
- Constitutions: Miscellaneous, 1935-1955 (Box 4, Folder 76-84)
- Minn Moline Employment/War Production, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 85)
- Pamphlets, 1939-1959 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Conventions, 1949-1958 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Newspaper clippings, 1947-1958 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Press Releases, 1949-1959 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Locals 1103-1121 (Box 6)
- Organization: Senn Battery, 1945 (Box 7, Folder 86-87)
- Organization: Turner Brass, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 88)
- Organization: Motorola, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 89)
- Organization: Ohmite, 1941-1947 (Box 7, Folder 90-98)
- Organization: Perm-O-Floor, 1946 (Box 7, Folder 99)
- Organization: Sentinel Radio, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 100-103)
- Organization: Kohler, 1945-1946 (Box 7, Folder 104)
- Organization: National Transformer, 1947-1948 (Box 7, Folder 105)
- Organization: McGraw Electric, 1946-1947 (Box 7, Folder 106)
- Organization: Snap-On Tools, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 107)
- Political Action: Minnesota, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 108)
- Organization: Southern Electric, 1942 (Box 7, Folder 109)
- Factionalism, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 110)
- Staff Reports: Dwight Gilpin, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 111)
- International Harvester: Wisconsin Steel-Progressive Steel Workers, 1947-1952 (Box 7, Folder 112-117)
- McCarran Act, 1950-1953 (Box 7, Folder 118)
- Office Employees Union, 1949-1955 (Box 7, Folder 119-120)
- Harry Bridges Defense Case, 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 121)
- DeWitt Gilpin Staff Assignments, 1952-1954 (Box 7, Folder 122)
- Publication Orders, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 123)
- Organization: Sylvania: Melrose Park, 1953-1958 (Box 7, Folder 124)
- Strikes: Westinghouse, 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 125)
- Organization: Northern Metals, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 127)
- Merger Discussions, 1955-1957 (Box 7, Folder 127)
- Haug Defense Case, 1957-1959 (Box 7, Folder 128)
- Ford-UAW Contract, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 129)
- Surplus Food, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 130)
- IAM #113 Factionalism, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 131-132)
- Kellogg Switchboard Supply/Inter-Union Rivalry: IAM & IBEW, 1955-1959 (Box 7, Folder 133-134)
- Time Study- Job Evaluation Information, 1950's (Box 7, Folder 135)
- 1961 DE Convention Arrangements, 1958-1959 (Box 7, Folder 136)
- Organization: Roth Mfg., 1950's (Box 7, Folder 137)
- Songs/Poems, 1950's (Box 7, Folder 138)
- 1950's Red-baiting (Box 7, Folder 139-144)
- Organization: Miscellaneous Shops, 1941-1959 (Box 7, Folder 145)
- Miscellaneous, 1945-1957 (Box 7, Folder 146-151)
- Locals 1150-101F (Box 8)
- Locals 1122-1150 (Box 9)
- Locals 182F-193 (Box 10)
- Leaflets, 1941-1959 (Box 11)
- Locals 107F-173F (Box 12)
- Mimeo Letters, 1942-1961 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Periodicals: UE National and Local, Other Orgs, 1942-1961 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Union Cards (Box 14)
- Union Cards (Box 15)
- Union Cards (Box 16)
- Union Cards (Box 17)
- Union Cards (Box 18)
- Union Cards (Box 19)
- Union Cards (Box 20)
- Union Cards and Correspondence, 1957-1960 (Box 21)
- Union Cards (Box 22)
- Union Cards (Box 23)
- Union Cards (Box 24)
- Union Cards (Box 25)
- Union Cards (Box 26)
- Union Cards (Box 27)
- Leaflets, 1952 (Box 28)
- Union Cards (Box 29)
- Local Records, 1952-1953 (Box 30)
- Union Cards and Correspondence, 1954 (Box 31)
- Correspondence, 1944-1947 (Box 32)
- Correspondence, 1948 (Box 33)
- Leaflets, Local, and Legal Records, 1951-1952 (Box 34)
- Union Cards, Local Reports, 1947-1953 (Box 35)
- Harrison Lennox Correspondence, 1946-1949 (Box 36)
- Local Records, 1953-1954 (Box 37)
- Union Cards (Box 38)
- Local Records, 1952 (Box 39)
- Pamphlets, 1958-1961 (Box 40)
- Negotiations, 1941-1943 (Box 41)
- Local Records and Contracts, 1950-1951 (Box 42)
- Local Records, 1950-1951 (Box 43)
- Union Cards (Box 44)
- Contracts, 1951 (Box 45)
- AAA Manufacturing Co. Diversey and Western (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Alvidsen Tools (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Benjamin Elec Co. (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Central Can Co. (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Consolidated (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Jaidinger Add Stickers (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Cinch (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Jaidlinger (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Jensen 1959 Campaign (Box 46, Folder 9)
- Mohr Lino Saw Co. (Box 46, Folder 10)
- Professional Equipment Co. (Box 46, Folder 11)
- Reflector Hardware (Box 46, Folder 12)
- Reflector Hardware (Box 46, Folder 13)
- Sherman Reynolds (Box 46, Folder 14)
- Sportsman (Box 46, Folder 15)
- Superior Pipe (Box 46, Folder 16)
- Superior Plastics (Box 46, Folder 17)
- Northern Metal N.L.R.B. (Box 46, Folder 18)
- Northern Metal Leaflets UE (Box 46, Folder 19)
- Northern Metal Leaflets Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 20)
- Northern Metal Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 21)
- Supreme (Box 46, Folder 22)
- Victor Gasket (Box 46, Folder 23)
- Supreme Leaflets 1959 Letters (Box 46, Folder 24)
- Supreme (Box 46, Folder 25)
- Supreme Leaflets and Letters, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 26)
- Supreme Miscellaneous (Box 46, Folder 27)
- Supreme Mailing list and Signed Members, 1959 (Box 46, Folder 28)
- Supreme Miscellaneous, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 29)
- Strike Aid ME, 1963 (Box 46, Folder 30)
- Swaby Pump (Box 46, Folder 31)
- Tanko Screw (Box 46, Folder 32)
- Tremax Industries 933 S. Paulino (Box 46, Folder 33)
- Troy Plating Works 514 S. Lflin (Box 46, Folder 34)
- Supreme Mailing List, 1958 (Box 46, Folder 35)
- Local Leaflets (Letters), 1955 (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Local Leaflets (Ballots), 1955-1956 (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Local 1114 Minutes (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Local Minutes (1114), 1950-1951 (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Local Minutes (1114), 1952 (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Local Minutes (1114), 1953 (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Local Minutes, 1950 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- UERMA-Director of Organization Report, February 1953-October 1957 (Box 47, Folder 8)
- UERMA Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1953-1957 (Box 47, Folder 9)
- UERMA Circular Letters, 1951-1955 (Box 47, Folder 10)
- UERMA GEB Min, 1953-1957 (Box 47, Folder 11)
- UERMA Organization Bulletin, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 12)
- UERMA Organization Bulletin, 1955-1956 (Box 47, Folder 13)
- UERMA Convention Policy, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 14)
- UERMA Convention Policy, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 15)
- UERMA Convention Policy, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 16)
- UERMA Convention Policy, 1954 (Box 47, Folder 17)
- Local Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1956 (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Local Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Local Elections (1114), 1955 (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Local Elections (1150), 1954-1955 (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Local Correspondence Miscellaneous, 1957 (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Goodman Leaflets, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Goodman Leaflets, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 2)
- Grand Sheet Leaflets Raid (iam), 1956 (Box 48, Folder 3)
- Grand Sheet Leaflets, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 4)
- Grand Sheet Leaflets, 1955 (Box 48, Folder 5)
- PG Leaflets, 1954-1955 (Box 48, Folder 6)
- Local Leaflets (Ballots), 1956-1958 (Box 48, Folder 7)
- Local Leaflets (Letters), 1956-1957 (Box 48, Folder 8)
- Publications Miscellaneous (Box 48, Folder 9)
- PG Leaflets, 1956 (Box 48, Folder 10)
- Allied Group Insurance Claims, 1955-1956 (Box 48, Folder 11)
- Brad Foote Gear Works, Inc. (Box 48, Folder 12)
- American Committee for the Protection of Foreign Born (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Toys-Christmas Party The Jay Mills Co. (Box 49, Folder 2)
- General File 1114 Miscellaneous, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Elecations (1114), 1953 (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Executive Board (1114), 1953 (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Financial Statements (1114), 1953 (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Chief Stewards and Stewards 1114, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Form Letters 1114, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 8)
- General File 1114, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 9)
- Press Releases 1114, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 10)
- UERMWA Contract Standards, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Districts Correspondence - UERMWA, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 12)
- James J. Matles, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Facts for Action (Box 49, Folder 14)
- UERMWA Financial Statements, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Fitzgerald, Albert UERMWA Local 1114, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 16)
- Local 1114 UERMWA General File, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 17)
- UE Local 1114 UERMWA General Executive Board, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 18)
- Leaflets Literature, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 19)
- Locals Correspondence UE (Local 1114), 1953 (Box 49, Folder 20)
- Applications Jobs in Local 1114 (Box 49, Folder 21)
- UE District 11 (Local 1114), 1953 (Box 49, Folder 22)
- Civil Rights Local 1114, 1953 (Box 49, Folder 23)
- Hubbard Spool Contract Negotiations, 1950 (Box 49, Folder 24)
- Perfection Screw (Box 49, Folder 25)
- Ampro Corp. Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 49, Folder 26)
- Ampro Corp. Grievances, 1945-1946 (Box 49, Folder 27)
- Baumbach Rates, 1943 (Box 49, Folder 28)
- Baumbach Negotiations, 1941-1943 (Box 49, Folder 29)
- Baumbach Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 49, Folder 30)
- Hanson Scale (Box 49, Folder 31)
- Onsrud Negotiations, 1948 (Box 49, Folder 32)
- Perfection Screw Negotiations, December 22, 1956 (Box 49, Folder 33)
- Chicago Metal Manufacturing Co. Grievances to Arbitration, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 1)
- Chicago Metal Manufacturing Co. Minutes of Stewards Meetings Membership, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 2)
- Clayton Mark and Company Minutes (Stewards and Strike Company Meetings Shop Meetings), 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 3)
- Clayton Mark Stephen Krakowski case (Box 50, Folder 4)
- Clayton Mark Trial of several employees (Box 50, Folder 5)
- Clayton Mark Company Press Releases (Box 50, Folder 6)
- Clayton Mark Financial Report (Confidential report of company's finances), 1946 (Box 50, Folder 7)
- Clayton Mark Manufacturing Co. Correspondence (Box 50, Folder 8)
- Clayton Mark Grievances and Grievances Meeting, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 9)
- Combustion Engineering Wage Rates and Job Classification, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 10)
- Combustion Engineering Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 11)
- Combustion Engineering Minutes of Meetings of Stewards, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 12)
- Combustion Engineering Co. Press Releases (Box 50, Folder 13)
- Danly Machine Specialties, Inc. Financial Report confidential, 1946 (Box 50, Folder 14)
- Danly Grievances, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 15)
- Danly Machine Specialties Co. Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 16)
- Danly Machine Specialties Job Descriptions, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 17)
- Danly Machine Minutes of Stewards Shift and Shop Meetings and Steward Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 50, Folder 18)
- Danly Branches (Box 50, Folder 19)
- Danly Machine Specialties, Inc. Letters of Withdrawal, 1945 (Box 50, Folder 20)
- Miehle printing press and Manufacturing Co. (Box 50, Folder 21)
- Baumbach (Box 50, Folder 22)
- Onsrud (Box 50, Folder 23)
- Bell and Howell National Relations Board (Box 51, Folder 1)
- Bell and Howell Correspondences, 1941-1943 (Box 51, Folder 2)
- Bell and Howell Leaflets, 1943 (Box 51, Folder 3)
- Bell and Howell Miscellaneous, 1941-1943 (Box 51, Folder 4)
- Bell and Howell Leaflets (Box 51, Folder 5)
- Bell and Howell Jurisdiction (Box 51, Folder 6)
- Current Leaflets Organization (Box 51, Folder 7)
- Recent 1114 Leaflets (Box 51, Folder 8)
- Recent (Box 51, Folder 9)
- Arnold Schwimm Co. (?) (Box 51, Folder 10)
- Albright Nell Leaflets (Box 51, Folder 11)
- Bell Howell (Box 51, Folder 12)
- Dries and Krump Correspondence, 1942-1944 (Box 51, Folder 13)
- Dries and Krump National Labor Relations Board (Box 51, Folder 14)
- Dries and Krump File (Box 51, Folder 15)
- Dreis and Krump Steward Reports (Box 51, Folder 16)
- Dreis and Krump Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 17)
- Dreis and Krump Leaflets-Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 18)
- Green Duck Company Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 19)
- Hammond Instrument Company Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 20)
- Gits Brothers National Labor Relations Board (Box 51, Folder 21)
- Gits Brothers Affidavits and Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 22)
- Taylor Forge Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 23)
- W.A. Jones Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 24)
- Quality Hardware and Machine Miscellaneous (Box 51, Folder 25)
- Diversey Machine Works (Box 51, Folder 26)
- Ditto, Inc. 2302 W. Harrison Street (Box 51, Folder 27)
- Chicago Latrobe Twist and Drill (Box 51, Folder 28)
- Industrial Metal Fabricators (Box 51, Folder 29)
- Bell and Howell Steward Reports (Box 51, Folder 30)
- Bell and Howell National Labor Relations Board (Box 51, Folder 31)
- Bell and Howell Leaflets, 1942 (Box 51, Folder 32)
- Gear Organization (Box 51, Folder 33)
- Bending Organization (Box 51, Folder 34)
- W.L.B. Cases (Box 51, Folder 35)
- Executive Orders and W.L.B. (Box 51, Folder 36)
- W.L.B. Panel Report TUR 111 13880-D (Box 51, Folder 37)
- W.L.B. Farnsworth 111-15158-D (Box 51, Folder 38)
- Luestfield Furniture W.L.B. 111-15265-D (Box 51, Folder 39)
- U.S. Rubber Co. UERWA Eau Claire 111-14059-D (Box 51, Folder 40)
- W.L.B. Warner Electric (Box 51, Folder 41)
- Miscellaneous W.L.B. (Box 51, Folder 42)
- Greiss Pfleger Tanning Leather Union Local 204 111 13856-D (Box 51, Folder 43)
- Container Corporation and F.E. 111 1457 (Box 51, Folder 44)
- W.L.B. Container Corporation (Box 51, Folder 45)
- Amgear Angert (Box 51, Folder 46)
- Republic Drill (Box 52, Folder 1)
- Republic Drill (Box 52, Folder 2)
- Republic Drill and Tool Company (Box 52, Folder 3)
- Republic Drill and Tool Wage Rates (Box 52, Folder 4)
- Republic Drill and Tool Works Cutbacks and Reconversion (Box 52, Folder 5)
- Republic Drill and Tool Miscellaneous Correspondence (Box 52, Folder 6)
- Republic Drill and Tool Suggestions (Box 52, Folder 7)
- Republic Drill and Tool Miscellaneous (Box 52, Folder 8)
- Illinois Tool Works (Box 52, Folder 9)
- Illinois Tool Works Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1945 (Box 52, Folder 10)
- Illinois Tool Works Miscellaneous Leaflets (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Illinois Tool Works Leaflets Miscellaneous, 1943 (Box 52, Folder 12)
- Illinois Tool Works Steward Reports (Box 52, Folder 13)
- Illinois Tool Works Correspondence, 1942-1943 (Box 52, Folder 14)
- Illinois Tool Works National War Labor Board (Box 52, Folder 15)
- Illinois Tool Works Leaflets Miscellaneous, 1942 (Box 52, Folder 16)
- Mall Tool Co. 7740 S. South Chicago Avenue (Box 52, Folder 17)
- Illinois Tool Works (Box 52, Folder 18)
- Illinois Tool Works (Box 52, Folder 19)
- Union Special Machine Compnay (Box 52, Folder 20)
- American Gear Leaflets (Box 52, Folder 21)
- Chicago Latrobe Twist Drill Co.mpany Miscellaneous Leaflets (Box 52, Folder 22)
- Illinois Tool Works National Labor Relations Board (Box 52, Folder 23)
- Illinois Tool Company (Box 52, Folder 24)
- Illinois Tool Company (Box 52, Folder 25)
- Peace Materials- Anti Nuclear, K War, International Institute for Peace, Red B and Anti K-War (Box 53, Folder 1)
- International Institute for Peace (Box 53, Folder 2)
- Department of Reference and Research (Box 53, Folder 3)
- Financial Records, 1958-1960 (Box 54)
- Financial Records, 1957-1959 (Box 55)
- Memos and Correspondence, 1980-1982 (Box 57)
- Correspondence, 1982-1985 (Box 58)
- Correspondence, 1966-1985 (Box 59)
- Local Records, Catalogs, and Financial Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 60)
- Local Records, 1963-1988 (Box 61)
- Westinghouse Correspondence, 1988 (Box 62)
- Memos, 1983-1985 (Box 63)
- Correspondence, 1974-1988 (Box 64)
- Leaflets, 1979-1981 (Box 65)
- Memos, 1980 (Box 66)
- Correspondence, 1980 (Box 67)
- Newspapers, 1980 (Box 68)
- Financial Memos, 1986-1987 (Box 69)
- Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 71)
- Leaflets, 1960-1967 (Box 72)
- Newspapers and Signup Sheets, 1980-1981 (Box 73)
- Local Records, 1960-1964 (Box 74)
- Convention Notes, 1958-1973 (Box 75)
- Finances, 1967-1971 (Box 76)
- Grievances, 1971-1989 (Box 77)
- A.F.L. Unions, National and Local, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 1)
- American Arbitration Association, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 2)
- Bernard, John T., Local 1114, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 3)
- Chicago Industrial Council, etc., 1948 (Box 78, Folder 4)
- C.I.O. National Office, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 5)
- Chief Stewards Local 1114, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 6)
- C.I.O. Unions, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 7)
- Company Financial Statements, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 8)
- Constitution and By-Law, Local 1114, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 9)
- Contract Analysis, Local 1114, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 10)
- Convention, UE 13th Annual, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 11)
- Clayton Mark, Independent Union Material, 1947-1948 (Box 78, Folder 12)
- Contract, Clayton Marks, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 13)
- District 11, UE, Financial Statements, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 14)
- District 11, UE, General, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 15)
- District 11 and Local 1114 Delegates, UE, Council and Board Minutes (Box 78, Folder 16)
- Elecations, Local 1114, 1947-1948 (Box 78, Folder 17)
- Executive Board, Local 1114, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 18)
- Financial Statements, Local 1114, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 19)
- Financial Statements, Local 1114 Shops, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 20)
- Illinois Standard, (successor to Chicago Star), 1948 (Box 78, Folder 21)
- Illinois State Department of Labor, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 22)
- Illinois State Industrial Union Council, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 23)
- Insurance, Local 1114, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 24)
- Local 1114, Insurance Plans, 1949 (Box 78, Folder 25)
- Legislative Bulletins, Local 1114, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 26)
- Membership Meeting, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 27)
- Membership Drive, Local 1114, Seniority Lists, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 28)
- Membership Drive, Local 1114, Reports to chapter states, lists of nonunion people, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 29)
- Midwest Guardian, Local 1114, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 30)
- Miscellaneous, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 31)
- Miscellaneous Organizations, 1948 (Box 78, Folder 32)
- Mundt Bill, Local 1114, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 1)
- NNNnNt.........National Office, Bulletins, Circulars, Letters, Etc., 1948 (Box 79, Folder 2)
- National Office, Bulletins, Circulars, Letters, Etc., 1948 (Box 79, Folder 3)
- National Office, UE, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 4)
- National Office, UE, Executive Board Minutes and Organizational Papers, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 5)
- National Office, UE, Financial Statements, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 6)
- National Office, UE, Radio Pamphlets, Etc., 1948 (Box 79, Folder 7)
- Press Releases, Local 1114, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 8)
- Rothstein, David, Local 1114 Atty, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 9)
- Stewards, Local 1114, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 10)
- Progressive Party, Local 1114, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 11)
- Taft-Hartley Law, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 12)
- 1114 Wage Survey, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 13)
- Staff Members, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 14)
- Trial Procedures of Walter Totos, Lee Burnett (Box 79, Folder 15)
- Miehle Employees Trial (Box 79, Folder 16)
- Trustees, Local 1114, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 17)
- UE Building, 37 S. Ashland, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 18)
- UE Locals (Box 79, Folder 19)
- UE News, Chicago and National, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 20)
- United States and Professional Works, C.I.O. and Affiliated Local 24, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 21)
- U.S. Congress and President, all correspondence with House of Representatives, Senate and President, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 22)
- U.S. Department of Justice, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 23)
- UE Job Referral Service (Box 79, Folder 24)
- Scully Jones and Co., File of Steward's Meetings (Box 79, Folder 25)
- Service Tool, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 26)
- Service Tool, Grievances, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 27)
- J.J. Tourek, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 28)
- J.J. Tourek, Grievances, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 29)
- Tuthill Pump, Grievances, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 30)
- Tuthill Pump, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 31)
- John Wood, Correspondence, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 32)
- John Wood, Grievances, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 33)
- John Wood Manufacturing Co., Strike, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 34)
- Chicago Metal Stewards (Box 79, Folder 35)
- Cribben and Sexton, File of Steward's Meeting (Box 79, Folder 36)
- Excelsior (Box 79, Folder 37)
- Per Capita Reports, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 1)
- Stewards Refund All Shops, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Social Security Withholding Taxes, Unemployment Compensation, 1952 (Box 80, Folder 3)